the final feature we will look at is the
我们将查看的最后一个功能是
recorder which allows you to record a
录音机 可让您录制
time lapse I'll use an 8x10 in canvas
时间流逝我将在画布上使用8x10
you may need to extend this panel
您可能需要扩展此面板
vertically to see all the options in
垂直查看中的所有选项
this panel there are two buttons near
这个面板旁边有两个按钮
the bottom the first will start and stop
底部的第一个将开始和停止
the recording before you record be sure
在你录音之前一定要确认
to set up your record settings Above
要设置上面的录音设置 请执行以下操作
This Will control the speed size and
这将控制速度大小和
quality of your video first choose the
您的视频质量首先选择
directory where you want the captured
要捕获的目录
image frames to go there is a shortcut
要去的图像边框有一个快捷方式
to open this folder the capture interval
要在捕获间隔内打开此文件夹 请执行以下操作
will control the speed a smaller value
将控制速度设置为较小的值
will record more frames or more brush
将录制更多帧或更多画笔
Strokes making the video longer and more
笔划使视频变得更长更多
detailed a larger value will record
详细的 更大的值将记录
fewer frames making the video shorter
帧越少 视频越短
and may miss some steps when choosing a
并且在选择
value keep in mind that when you export
值请记住 当您导出时
your video you'll need to select the
您的视频 您需要选择
frame rate which is set to 30 by default
默认设置为30的帧速率
but can be higher 60 frames per second
但可以高于每秒60帧
will give you smoother movement but will
会让你的动作更流畅 但会
also make the video duration shorter and
还可以缩短视频持续时间 并
the file size larger divide the capture
文件大小越大划分捕获
interval by the number of frames per
间隔按每帧的帧数
second and that will give you the
第二 这将给你带来
duration of your video so for example if
视频的持续时间 例如 如果
I paint for 90 seconds at 1 frame per
我以每帧1帧的速度作画90秒
second I will have generated 90 frames
其次 我将生成90个帧
at a frame rate of 30 frames per second
以每秒30帧的帧速率
that would only be 3 seconds of
那只是3秒的时间
video The Format controls the quality
视频格式控制质量
and file size of the recorded images PNG
和记录图像PNG的文件大小
will give you better quality but will
会给你带来更好的质量 但会
require more storage space on your
需要更多的存储空间
computer jpeg can be used fully of
计算机jpeg可以充分利用
quality is not a concern and smaller
质量不是问题 而是更小
file size is preferred in either case
在任一情况下 文件大小都是首选的
you can choose the quality and
您可以选择质量和
compression
压缩
values and finally resolution controls
值 最后是分辨率控件
the video Dimensions this is linked to
此链接到的视频尺寸
the size of your document so if you want
您的文档大小 因此如果您希望
to capture maximum quality choose
要获得最高质量 请选择
original you can also choose a smaller
原来你也可以选择小一点的
size if you want a smaller video for
如果想要更小的视频 请调整大小
example if I only require a 1080p video
如果我只需要一个1080p视频的例子
I might be able to have the resolution
我也许能拿到解决方案
to save storage space I'll click the
为了节省存储空间 我将单击
record button to initiate the recording
启动录制的录制按钮
it's important to note that only the
值得注意的是 只有
canvas will be captured not the UI or
将捕获画布 而不是用户界面或
cursor if you want to capture that stuff
如果您想要捕获这些内容 请使用光标
you'll need something like OBS Studio
你需要像OBS Studio这样的东西
which is
这就是
free next I'll stop the recording then
下一步有空 我会停止录音
click on export first things first if
如果出现以下情况 请先单击导出优先事项
ffmpeg is missing you aren't going to
Fmpeg不见了 你不会的
get very far you'll need to install that
要想走得很远 你需要安装它
and link to the ffmpeg exe file this is
并链接到ffmpeg exe文件 这是
what turns your captured frames into a
是什么将您捕获的帧转换为
watchable video FPS can be 30 or 60 if
如果出现以下情况 则可观看视频FPS为30或60
you want to speed up or slow down the
您想要加速或减慢
rate of your video you can make these
您可以制作这些视频的速率
values different for example 6030 will
值不同 例如6030将
make the video twice as
将视频制作成两倍于
fast you can also show a still preview
快速您还可以显示静态预览
at the beginning or end of the video the
在视频的开头或结尾
video Dimensions can be resized you can
视频尺寸可以调整 您可以
stretch the video but that will add
拉伸视频 但这会增加
block space around your canvas in this
在此阻止您的画布周围的空间
case if I want to make a 1080p video
如果我想制作1080p视频 请大小写
then I can make the width 1920 and the
然后我可以把宽度1920和
height 1080 pixels if you will be
高度为1080像素 如果您要
primarily recording your screen for
主要为以下目的录制屏幕
posting it to YouTube you may want to
把它发布到YouTube上 你可能会想
start with a canvas size that matches
从匹配的画布大小开始
the video Dimensions so there isn't any
视频的尺寸 所以没有
black space added to the edges when you
当您执行以下操作时 会向边缘添加黑色空间
export the video under render as choose
在Render As Choose下导出视频
h264 since it will be the most
H264因为它将是最多的
compatible with other applications the
与其他应用程序兼容
video location setting controls where
视频位置设置控制位置
the exported video will go you can see
导出的视频将会显示 您可以看到
at the bottom of this panel with the
在此面板的底部 使用
output video duration will be again you
输出视频时长将再次是您
can adjust the input fps to change the
可以调整输入fps以更改
video length click export and after the
视频长度单击导出 然后在
video has been rendered you can watch
视频已呈现 您可以观看
it whatever you capture in your
无论你在你的电脑里捕捉到什么
recordings is stored as snapshots so
录制内容存储为快照 因此
you'll want to clear those out after
之后你会想要清理掉那些东西
rendering the video If you no longer
渲染视频(如果您不再
need them otherwise they eat up space on
需要它们 否则它们会占用空间
your
你的
computer e
计算机e